[
{"question": "What is your name?", "answer": "Ahmed Nadar", "label": "Name"},
{"question": "What is the name of the company you're applying for?", "answer": "ACME Software Solution. Is a leading growth-stage B2B SaaS company", "label": "Company Applying To"},
{"question": "What is the role you're applying for?", "answer": "Senior Software Developer", "label": "Role Applying To"},
{"question": "How many years of experience do you have?", "answer": "12", "label": "Years of Experience"},
{"question": "What are your greatest professional strengths?", "answer": "I am a very fast learner and I am very passionate about my work", "label": "Greatest Strength"},
{"question": "What are your top achievements (list)?", "answer": "I built online businesses with Rails stack, I taught and mentored 100+ students in programming and design, I share and publish my work on Github and blogs", "label": "Top Achievements"},
{"question": "What are your professional growth desires?", "answer": "I want to become a full stack developer and work on a large scale project.", "label": "Professional Goal"},
{"question": "What kind of work environment do you prefer?", "answer": "I like work remotely, and I like to work in a team. I like tecnically challenging work. I like to work with people who are passionate about their work", "label": "My Ideal Work Environment"},
{"question": "What does your ideal work day look like?", "answer": "Flexible hours, I tend to work very early in the morning", "label": "My Ideal Work Day"},
{"question": "Why are you excited about this particular job role?", "answer": "I am excited because I want to work on a large scale project. I want to work and collaborating with creative team of people who are passionate about their work, and I want to work remotely, and I want to work on a project that will change the world", "label": "My excitement about job role"},
{"question": "What about the job stands out to you? Why are you a great fit?", "answer": "I am a great fit because my experience and ability to understand business objectives and collaborate effectively with team members, will enable me to make a positive impact on the company's success. My strong work ethic, urgency, natural curiosity, and drive, combined with my passion for software development, will enable me to deliver high-quality results, meet tight deadlines, and contribute to Creyos' goal of solving big challenges.", "label": "Why I'm a Great Fit"},
{"question": "What are your relevant skills and expertise?", "answer": "I have experience in software development, including in Ruby, Python, Hotwire stack, and TailwindCSS. I am familiar with Agile development methodologies and have experience with cloud technologies like AWS. I am also familiar in software architecture and design patterns, and have a strong understanding of software testing and debugging techniques.", "label": "Relevant skills and expertise"},
{"question": "What is your career growth?", "answer": "I am looking for a role where I can continue to develop my skills and grow my career. I am particularly interested in this position at Microsoft because of the company's reputation for innovation and its commitment to technology.", "label": "Career growth"},
{"question": "What is specific example of previous work?", "answer": "One of my proudest achievements was the successful launch of a web app that I developed for a client. This project involved working closely with a cross-functional team, including designers, project managers, and QA engineers. I also implemented new features and resolved technical issues, ensuring that the app was user-friendly and stable.", "label": "Previous work"}
]